export const qna = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Where and when will the ceremony take place?",
    answer:
      "The ceremony will be at Saint Pio of Pietrelcina Parish, formerly known as San Pedro Calungsod Parish - Sanctuary of Padre Pio and it will strictly start at 9:30 am.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What time should we arrive?",
    answer:
      "We kindly encourage you to arrive at 9 AM, as the entourage begins lining up at this time. The processional will start promptly at 9:30 AM, and we would love to see you all as we take our first walk down the aisle.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Is there a parking area for our car?",
    answer:
      "Yes, there are free parking spaces available inside the church's vicinity. For the reception, free parking spaces are available outside the facility as well as in the basement. If needed, you can also park at a nearby establishment with assistance from the management.",
  },

  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Can we bring our kids - invite a plus one (driver/yaya/date)?",
    answer:
      "As much as we’d love to have everyone celebrate with us, unfortunately, our venue can only accommodate a limited number of guests. While we adore your children, due to necessity rather than choice, only kids who are part of the entourage and were specifically confirmed will be attending. We hope you understand and still enjoy the celebration.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Can we take pictures during the wedding ceremony?",
    answer:
      "Our ceremony will be unplugged and solemn. Please turn off and keep your phones during the processional and ceremony. You may take photos after we have been pronounced as husband and wife. We have an incredible team of photographers and videographers to capture the moments. We promise to share the photos with you after the wedding. Help us capture the love afterward. Share your photos using our official hashtag: #nararaPATkayJO.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "When is the appropriate time to leave?",
    answer:
      "We aim to end the program around 2:00 PM, and we would appreciate it if you could stay until then. If you must leave early, we'd love to thank you and say goodbye before you go—perhaps not while they're playing the Same Day Edit Video, though.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Can I proceed directly to the reception? What time is the reception?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you can proceed directly to the reception, but it would warm our hearts to see you during our vow exchange. The pre-program will start at 11:30 AM, and appetizers and refreshments will be served",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Can we sit anywhere at the reception?",
    answer:
      "No. It took us a lot of effort and discussion to finalize the seating arrangement, which is designed for everyone’s convenience, network preference, and group familiarity. Our coordinators will gladly assist you in finding your designated seats.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Do we really need to RSVP?",
    answer:
      "Yes, it is essential. RSVPing helps us coordinate guests, finalize the headcount, arrange seating, and adhere to venue restrictions. Let’s make this celebration truly unforgettable.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "I already confirmed yes to the RSVP. However, I cannot attend anymore due to an unforeseen event. What should I do?",
    answer:
      "It would be sad for us to hear that you can no longer attend our wedding, especially since we specifically invited those who are close to our hearts. However, we understand that there may be such circumstances. Please do let us know as soon as possible so we can offer your allotted seat to another guest.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "If I RSVP “NO” but my schedule suddenly frees up, what should I do?",
    answer:
      "Please let us know right away if your schedule frees up so we can confirm. However, please understand that we may have already reallocated your seat.",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Do you have a gift preference?",
    answer:
      "Your presence, joy, and companionship on our wedding day mean the world to us. However, if you would like to celebrate with a gift, a donation to our savings fund would be truly appreciated.",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "Who do we get in touch with if we are unable to contact you on the wedding day?",
    answer:
      "Please understand that we may not be able to respond to you during the day as we will be busy preparing. If there are urgent concerns, you may contact the following: Coordinator: JOY FRANCISCO EVENTS MANAGEMENT TEAM (09176060700)",
  },
];

export const menuItems = [
  {
    label: "Home",
    path: "#hero",
  },
  {
    label: "For You",
    path: "#for-you",
  },
  {
    label: "Entourage",
    path: "#entourage",
  },
  {
    label: "Other Details",
    path: "#other-details",
  },
  {
    label: "Gallery",
    path: "#gallery",
  },
  {
    label: "Location",
    path: "#location",
  },
  {
    label: "Q + A",
    path: "#q-n-a",
  },
  {
    label: "RSVP",
    path: "#rsvp",
  },
];
